firetrust.com 2016-03-07

# Privacy Policy | Firetrust

## Firetrust website policy

We believe it is important that you know how we treat information about you which we receive via the Internet. Our commitment to personal privacy is paramount - none of our products contain any form of Adware or Spyware.

Firetrust Limited lets you visit the Firetrust website without revealing any personal information about yourself. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies (personal information) about you. Firetrust requests personal information from our users at several different points on our website. The personal information we collect is used only to respond to your inquiry, process an order, allow you to access specific account information, or advise you of special promotions, discounts, updates and new products.

Firetrust is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not use or disclose this information for purposes other than those set out in this statement or in our end user agreement.

By using this site or any services provided through the site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Statement.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Firetrust does not collect any personal data about you on this website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us, by purchasing a product from us, by downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online feedback form). When you purchase a product from Firetrust, we may collect information including your contact details and credit card details. Please note that credit card information may be retained by our billing provider (Global Collect or Paypal) as a record of any transaction we undertake with you. Firetrust does not store your credit card details. 

Information which you provide us is used by Firetrust only in line with the purpose for which you provided it and will not be made available to third parties other than to our online billing provider and our banking institution to enable a purchase of a product to be processed, or a third party purchaser of all or part of Firetrust's business. Please note that the transfer of information by us to such third parties may involve a transfer of that information to countries outside New Zealand.

If Firetrust has your email address, we may contact you by email to advise you of product updates, subscribe you to our newsletter or offer you Firetrust or third party products. You can opt out from receiving these emails at any time. Your preferences can be updated online by clicking [http://www.firetrust.com/user ](http://www.firetrust.com/user "Firetrust's Customer Centre"). Firetrust may also contact you in relation to customer support queries which you lodge.

Your personal data may also be anonymised and used for statistical purposes.

## Links

The Firetrust website may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are leaving our website and travelling to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer on behalf of a website that you have visited. Session (temporary) cookies may be used from time-to-time to enhance navigation within the website. These cookies are destroyed when the user closes their web browser. 

## Your Firetrust Login and related information

The Firetrust web site allows you to create a “Firetrust Login” based on your email address and a password. This is required when synchronizing account information or using the mobile versions. 

## Data Security

Firetrust is committed to protecting the security of your information and takes reasonable precautions to protect it. However, Internet data transmissions, whether wired or wireless, cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure and as a result we cannot ensure the security of information you transmit to us; accordingly, you acknowledge that you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your data transmission, we make all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems:

Your Firetrust Login and any account information and content is protected by encryption and only you have access to it; Your personal information and data stored in our systems is protected by various physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. It is housed in a secure facility and physical and network access to this facility is restricted to select trained staff. Firetrust regularly evaluates its technologies, facilities, procedures and potential risks to maintain the security and privacy of our users’ data. 

Firetrust employees have no way to monitor or view your personal information or content stored in the Firetrust service as all content is encrypted. 

If Firetrust learns of a security system breach we may attempt to notify you and provide information on protective steps, if available, through the e-mail address that you supplied during registration or posting a notice on our web site. 

## Log files

Google Analytics is used to analyze traffic to this website. Google Analytics does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services, Google Analytics does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. Google Analytics only collects aggregate data.

With regards to HideAway VPN - We do not store any connection logs or usage data as the service is unrestricted in usage and to limit our legal liability.

## Changes to this Policy

Firetrust reserves the right to change this policy at any time by providing notice of such modification on this site.
